<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tvier.net</title>
    <link>http://www.tvier.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on tvier.net</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 22:06:15 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.tvier.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s that parking lot costing your city?</title>
      <link>http://www.tvier.net/blog/underutilized_land/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 22:06:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.tvier.net/blog/underutilized_land/</guid>
      <description>If you live in North America, you&amp;rsquo;re probably used to seeing scenes like this.
A bunch of asphalt, a couple traffic lights, a big store and some greenery.
Some people might love it, some might hate it, but to most of us this looks so normal we don&amp;rsquo;t think about it. That&amp;rsquo;s a shame, because what you see here results in reduced services and crumbling infrastructure if you&amp;rsquo;re lucky, and digs your city deeper into debt on top of that if you&amp;rsquo;re not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A walk through lightweight blogging</title>
      <link>http://www.tvier.net/blog/a_walk_through_lightweight_blogging/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 23:57:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.tvier.net/blog/a_walk_through_lightweight_blogging/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s say you want to set up a blog, there are plenty of good reasons after all. But, you hate websites that are slow, full of spyware, and unusable on spotty connections. This leaves you with a bit of a problem, the big names aren&amp;rsquo;t going to cut it.
This is what I ran into while setting up this blog. I didn&amp;rsquo;t find any other resources going over what was currently available, so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d run through my experience in the hopes that it will be easier for the next person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new blog</title>
      <link>http://www.tvier.net/blog/new_blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jan 2022 21:44:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.tvier.net/blog/new_blog/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a new blog. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll write about it</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I use</title>
      <link>http://www.tvier.net/i_use/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.tvier.net/i_use/</guid>
      <description>An idea taken from David Mytton.
Once a year (or whatever period), record what I&amp;rsquo;m using for my personal computer setup. It should be interesting to see how things change.
2022-02-19 Main computer: Inspiron 5515 Rarely used gaming PC: Intel (i5-????k) and nvidia (gtx1660) desktop with 144hz 1080p monitor Media PC: Asus PN51 OS: Manjaro i3 edition Phone: Pixel 4a(5g) running graphene Headphones: Philips XR2HR with the resonant hole closed up a bit as described here Key Software Code: nvim Lots of plugins, most notable: coc fzf ranger Browser: firefox Mail: Protonmain Backup/Synch: No backup :( synchthing Notes: obsidian Terminal: termite (RIP) Shell: zsh, ohmyzsh 2022-02-19 Main computer: Dying, ~10 year old, Dell XPS; Intel (i5-?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
